&gt；&gt；Steve Kinney：酷，让我们开始吧。
&gt;&gt; Steve Kinney: Cool,
so let's get started.
谈谈我们所说的工作表现是什么意思？
Talk a little bit about what do
we mean by the work performance?
为什么这很重要，除了在幻灯片上看起来很好之外，我实际上
And why it matters, except that seemed
good on the slide, I'm actually
我要回答为什么它很重要，然后我们将讨论如何思考它。
gonna answer the why it matters and then
we'll talk about how to think about it.
大多数情况下，这是一个自我推销，让你在接下来的几个时间里保持兴趣
Mostly it's a self pitch to keep
you interested over the next few
几个小时就像是给你一个关于为什么它很重要的说辞
hours it's kind of like giving you
the pitch on why it's important and
然后我们将讨论如何处理它。
then we'll talk about what to do about it.
那么，为什么性能如此重要呢？
So why does performance matter?
我认为目前的行业标准是
I think the industry
standard at this point is
浏览一大堆统计数据幻灯片作为对权威的巨大呼吁，
to go through a bunch of slides of
statistics as a large appeal to authority,
就像这些东西真的很重要，你已经在看这个课程了。
like this stuff is really important also
you're already watching this course.
是的，公平地说，我是在向唱诗班布道。
Si it's fair to say that I
am preaching to the choir.
但是你有一个产品经理或一个工程经理并不是不可能的
But it is not unlikely that you have a
product manager or an engineering manager
这也需要，[笑]这将受益于这一销售宣传。
that would also need to be, [LAUGH] that
would benefit from this sales pitch.
所以我们一起做
So we'll do it together, and
在这背后的一些研究中武装我们自己。
arm ourselves in kind of some
of the research behind this.
Jakob Nielsen在用户界面和性能方面做了大量研究。
Jakob Nielsen did a bunch of research
on User interfaces and performance.
很多事情真的很有趣。
A lot of it was really
kind of interesting.
在大约十分之一秒时，用户感觉系统是瞬时的，对吗？
At about a tenth of a second, users feel
that the system is instantaneous, right?
他们采取行动，应用程序做出响应。
They take an action and
the application has responded.
他们没有注意到任何形式的滞后。
They don't notice any kind of lag.
这就是理想。
That is the ideal.
所以十分之一秒，100毫秒就是我们的目标
So a 10th of a second, 100 milliseconds
is kind of what we aim for.
这是不是一直都有可能？
Now is that always possible?
我们需要通过网络请求来做这件事吗？
Do we need to make a network
request to do the thing, right?
要考虑的因素很多。
There's a lot of
considerations to think about.
但我们知道用户什么都不能说，
But we know that users
can not tell anything,
我认为微软已经做了研究，他们使之变得越来越快。
I think Microsoft has done research where
they make that even faster and faster.
并且有一些不可察觉的，用户可以注意到，但是对于我们的目的，
And there are imperceptible,
users can notice, but for our purposes,
100毫秒是黄金标准。
100 milliseconds is the gold standard.
大约一秒钟后，
After about a second,
用户的思想流动被打断了，他们注意到了，对吗？
user's flow of thought is interrupted,
they notice it, right?
他们可能会分心，他们可能会失去应用程序的感觉
They could get distracted, they can
lose the feeling that the application
响应并做他们要求的事情。
is responsive and
doing the things that they're asking for.
然后大约十秒钟后
And then after about ten seconds
要保持用户的注意力几乎是不可能的。
it's almost impossible to
keep a user's attention.
对吧？
Right?
在这一点上，一个闪亮的物体出现在角落里，用户离开了。
At that point, a shiny object in the
corner has appeared and the user is gone.
对吧？现在被允许，
Right?
Now granted,
如果页面上的交互时间超过10秒
if you have interactions on your
page that take more than ten seconds
我们应该谈谈，对吧？
we should talk, right?
十秒是一段很长的时间。
Ten seconds is a very long period of time.
但是加载一个页面需要多长时间，这也不是很离谱，对吧？
But it's also not outrageous for
how long it takes a page to load, right?
在很多情况下，如果我们正在编写JavaScript应用程序，对吗？
In a lot of cases if we are writing
JavaScript applications, right?
我们不仅需要将这些位传送到浏览器，而且
We not only have to get those
bits to the browser, but
然后我们还必须在他们的机器上构建应用程序。
we also then have to build
the application on their machines.
所以这十秒对于互动来说都是，但是
And so that ten seconds is both for
an interaction but going and
一开始访问页面，也是与页面的互动，对吧？
visiting the page in the beginning, is
also an interaction with the page, right?
所以我们也要记住这一点。
So we want to keep that in mind as well.
因为我们知道，通过大量的研究，如果我们的页面花费太长时间
Because we know that with a lot of
research that if our page takes too long
加载它将对用户参与产生影响。
to load it will have
impacts on user engagement.
酷毙了。所以我要展示
Cool.
So I'm going to show
你有更多的数据让我看起来很聪明，但是
you some more statistics that
make myself seem smart but
真的，收集别人非常聪明的作品。
really, collecting other
people's really smart work.
Aberdeen Group发现，1秒的减速会导致11%
The Aberdeen Group found that a 1
second slow down resulted in 11%
页面浏览量减少，转换率减少7%。
fewer page views and 7% less conversion.
对吧？
Right?
许多应用程序的页面查看和转换都变成了美元和美分。
Page views and conversions for a lot of
applications turn into dollars and cents.
对吧？还有
Right?
And,
我写软件是因为我真的很喜欢写软件，但是
I write software because I really
enjoy writing software but
我也真的很喜欢通过编写软件获得报酬。
I also really enjoy getting paid for
writing software.
这样我就不用做其他事情了。
So I don't have to do other things.
而且我也喜欢我工作的公司，我赚的钱足够付我钱。
And I also enjoy the company I work for
making enough money to pay me.
所以很多时候，我们的表现和我们直接关心的东西
So a lot of times, the performance and
our care about that stuff directly
转化为我们所做的工作，这也是为了取悦用户，对吧？
translates into the work that we do and
it's also about delighting users, right?
Akamai发现网页加载时间增加了2秒的延迟
Akamai found that a 2 second delay
in web page load time increased
弹跳率高达103%。
bounce rates by 103%.
所以离开的人数是现在的两倍
So double the amount of people are leaving
如果页面加载速度慢两秒。
if your page is two
seconds slower to load.
400毫秒的性能提高导致9%的
A 400 millisecond improvement in
performance resulted in a 9% increase in
雅虎的流量，对吧？
traffic at Yahoo, right?
所以我们可以看到在性能之间存在这种相关性
So we can see that there is this
correlation between the performance
我们的申请，并有效地支付账单。
of our application and
effectively paying the bills.
谷歌发现，页面速度慢2%会导致搜索量减少2%，
Google found that a 2% slower page
resulted in 2% fewer searches,
考虑到谷歌的商业模式，这意味着所显示的广告减少了2%
which given Google's business
model means 2% fewer ads shown and
你可以看到那种Fike是如何沿着整个东西流下来的。
you can see how that kind of fike
trickles down the entire thing.
性能提高100毫秒，结果为1%
100 millisecond improvement in
performance results in a 1%
亚马逊整体收入的增长。
increase in the overall revenue at Amazon.
现在1%，通常看起来不是很大的影响，
Now 1%,
normally doesn't seem like a big impact,
但是当你在亚马逊规模下运营时，1%是很多的，对吧？
but when you're operating at Amazon scale,
1% is a lot, right?
所以肯定有，我们可以追踪，
So there's definitely, we can trace,
对业绩的关心很多次都是业务成果。
the care about performance to
a lot of times business outcomes.
如果加载时间超过3秒，53%的用户会离开移动站点，
53% of users will leave a mobile site if
it takes more than 3 seconds to load,
对吧？
right?
所以我们把所有的工作和关怀投入到这个网站的建设中，并且
So we put all this work and
care into building this website, and
他们甚至不会看到它，因为它花了太长时间。
they're not even going to see
it because it took too long.
我认为一个普通的在研究中是很有意义的
And I think the one general one
makes a lot of sense in the research
如果您希望您的应用程序或站点感觉更快，
is that if you want your application or
your site to feel faster,
你需要比你的竞争对手快20%左右，对吗？
you need to be about 20% faster
than your competitors, right?
所以你需要保留这一点，我们知道现在会有所不同。
So you need to keep that,
we know that that now makes a difference.
所以快速是很重要的，对吧？
So being in fast is important, right?
是的，让我们做这件事，对吧？
Yeah, let's do the thing, right?
我们有这些经过试验的真实的东西，比如减少你的资产和东西，
We have these tried and true things like
minify your assets and of things and
通过网络发送它，自从我开始编程以来，这些都是真的。
send it across the wire and those have
been true since I started programming.
对吧？
Right?
但在我们的领导下，事情也发生了变化。
But things have changed from
out from under us as well.
所以与此同时，快速是非常重要的，
So at the same time while being
fast is really important,
成为一个快速的应用程序也要困难得多。
it's also a lot harder to
be a fast application.
应用程序变得越来越大。
Applications keep getting bigger and
bigger and bigger.
几年前，一般的Web应用程序
A few years ago,
the average web application
打到了比电子游戏“末日”更大的地方，对吧？
hIt the point where it was bigger
than the video game Doom, right?
所以有效地，我们正在发送一个完整的视频游戏
So effectively,
we are sending an entire video game
几十年前，每次有人访问我们的页面。
from a few decades ago every time
someone goes to visit our page.
这不仅是一个有趣的事实，而且
Not only is that a fun factoid, but
我认为看着图表看它不是很重要，
I think looking at the graph is
kind of important to see it's not,
它是在几年前跳出来的，现在我们正处于Web应用领域。
it jumped off a few years ago and
here we are now in web application land.
随着时间的推移，它越来越多。
It's increasingly
increasing as time goes on.
所以这是beta.httparchive.org实际上有一堆
So this is beta.httparchive.org
actually has a bunch of
数据的平均网页的基本大小牵引从2010年开始。
data on the basic size of the average web
page traction from about 2010 on forward.
你可以看到我在2013年3月15日左右徘徊。
And you can see that I hovered
around March 15, 2013.
所以五年前的今天。
So five years ago today.
你可以看到，第50个百分位数的平均值大约是864千字节，对吧？
And you can see that the average, the 50th
percentile was about 864 kilobytes, right?
那里有一个范围。
And there's a range there.
但你可以看到，今天台式机上的平均值几乎是这个数字的两倍。
But you can see that the average today
on desktop is almost double that.
两倍多，在手机上，十倍大小，对吧？
More than double that and on mobile,
ten times that size, right?
所以，是的，手机变得越来越快，诸如此类。
So as, yeah phones are getting faster and
stuff like that.
与我们向浏览器发送越来越多代码的速度不同。
Not at the same rate that we are shipping
more and more code to the browser.
所以这意味着我们需要开始关心表现，如果我们希望跟上的话。
So it means that we need to start caring
about performance if we hope to keep up.
同时，LTE变得越来越慢，特别是在两个网络上。
At the same time, LTE is getting slower,
on two networks in particular.
但总的来说，随着越来越多的人使用LTE，
But in general, as more and
more people get LTE,
网络越来越陷入困境。
the networks are getting more and
more increasingly bogged down.
这意味着随着我们发布越来越多的代码，获取代码的时间是
Which means that as we ship more and
more code, the time to get that code is
时间越来越长，可能会有点失控。
taking longer and longer,
which can get a little out of control.
所以，我们需要，再一次我们需要处理这些东西，因为
So, we need to, again we need to
be dealing with this stuff because
它不会神奇地变得更好。
it's not going to just
magically get better.
浏览器会变得更快下一代iPhone会更好
The browser is gonna get faster and
the next iPhone is gonna be way better,
我不需要担心这些
I don't have to worry about any of this.
虽然这些事情是真的，但它们不一定，
While those things are true,
they don't necessarily,
在这里，利率是一个更大的问题。
the rate, is kind of a bigger issue here.
所以好吧，表现很重要，我有没有说过这一点？
So all right, performance is important,
have I made that point?
感觉好吗？
Feel good about that?
相信吗？太好了。
Convinced?
Sweet.
所以最大的问题是我们如何看待性能，对吗？
So the big question is how do we
think about performance, right?
我之前开玩笑说你可以压缩你的资产
I joked before that you
can gzip your assets and
缩小它们并沿着这些线进行填充。
minify them and stuff along those lines.
对吧？这很好。
Right?
And that's great.
但我认为这真的很有趣，我认为这很重要
But I think it's really interesting,
I think it's important
考虑您正在工作的应用程序以及它的需求是什么。
to think about the application that
you're working on and what are its needs.
一个非常好的例子是，如果你想到一个内容网站，比如
A really great example is if you
think about a content website like
“纽约时报”或“赫芬顿邮报”或
the New York Times or
the Huffington Post or
沿着这些路线的任何事情，他们需要做什么？
anything along those lines,
what do they need to do?
他们最优先考虑的是什么？
What is their biggest priority?
让你满意，对吧？
Showing you content, right?
他们需要尽快做到这一点。
And they need to do that as
instantaneously as possible.
有人会说，Twitter或Facebook也是如此。
One would argue that's true for
Twitter, or Facebook as well.
是，您登录是为了查看您的时间线，并且
Is, you logged in to see your timeline,
and
他们需要尽快向你展示。
they need to show it to you as
quickly as they possibly can.
向您显示加载栏是不可接受的。
Showing you a load bar is not acceptable.
对吧？
Right?
你会离开的。
You will leave.
你会觉得我应该做点别的事情而不是看新闻。
You'll be like I should be doing something
else rather than checking on the news.
我要回去做真正的工作了。
I'm gonna go back to that real work.
我不需要这么做，对吧？
I don't need to do this, right?
这就是我们正在谈论的
And that's kind of what we're
talking about with those like
明显的百分比，对吧？
noticeable percentages, right?
当人们离开的时候，我实际上不需要现在就这么做。
That's when people go, I don't actually
need to be doing this right now.
我的老板来了。
There is my boss coming.
Command+Tab返回到我的文本编辑器，对吗？
Command+Tab back to my text editor, right?
但是Gmail如果你仔细想想
But Gmail if you think about it,
我们可以容忍每次登录Gmail时都会有一个加载栏，对吧？
we tolerate a loading bar every
time we log into Gmail, right?
因为这是有区别的。
Because there is a difference.
在内容集上，您可能会从一个页面跳到另一个页面。
On a content set you might be
jumping from page to page to page.
另一方面，在像Gmail这样的网站上，
On a site like Gmail on the other hand,
你打开Gmail，一天的大部分时间都在里面生活。
you open up Gmail and you live in it for
the majority of the day.
也许你要换到另一个帐单，但我们愿意支付一次费用，
Maybe you're switching to another tab,
but we're willing to pay that cost once,
因为我们知道，一旦我们支付了加载应用程序的成本，它就在那里
because we know that once we pay the cost
for loading the application it's there and
它是活的，所以它更像是单页面应用程序的感觉。
it's alive so
it's more of the of single page app feel.
但对于Gmail来说，他们需要更多地关注内存链接，对吗？
But for Gmail they need to be a much more
concerned about like memory links, right?
因为如果随着应用程序的存在，随着时间的推移，速度变慢
Because if it get slower over time
as the application exist as they're
把越来越多的东西加到某某上，这变得站不住脚。
adding more and more to the so and
so forth, that becomes untenable.
当像“纽约时报”这样的页面有人从一个页面跳到另一个页面时
While a page like The New York Times
someone's bouncing from page to page to
佩奇，对吧？
page, right?
应用程序的优先级非常不同，对吧？
The priorities are very different for
the applications, right?
所以我们可以容忍这一点，但我们不会容忍来自“纽约时报”的报道。
So we can tolerate this, but
we would not tolerate from New York Times.
我们必须，管理好这些。
We have to, manage those.
所以今天我要争论的是有三种不同的表演。
So I'm gonna argue today that there
are three different kinds of performance.
我们将逐个讨论，而不是仅仅说，
And we're gonna talk about each one
individually rather than just say,
性能做这些事情，可以是一个20个项目的博客帖子，对吗？
performance do these things that could
have been a blog post of 20 items, right?
我们要转身，弄清楚我们是如何看待性能的。
We're going to turn,
figure out how we think about performance.
其中一些东西是如何在引擎盖下工作的
How some of these things
work under the hood and
然后用它来告诉我们该怎么做。
then use that to inform
what we do about it.
所以我想要论证的三种表现类型是存在的
So the three types of performance
that I want to argue exist
是网络负载性能。
are network load performance.
所以，好吧，我们构建客户端应用程序。
So, okay,
we build client side applications.
就这一点而言，您希望使用此应用程序，这是一个独特的问题？
Which is a unique problem insofar that,
you would like this application?
让我将源代码发送给您的应用程序和
Let me send you the source
code to the application and
你可以应付一切。
you can deal with everything.
所以我们需要在用户看到任何东西之前将其传递给他们。
So we need to get that to the user
before they see anything.
所以这显然很重要，我们需要处理这个问题。
So that's obviously important and
we need to deal with that.
这通常是当人们谈论他们所谈论的性能时
And that is normally when people talk
about performance they're talking about
缓存标头和所有这些类型和
caching headers and all those kinds and
我怎样才能让你尽快进入这个页面？
how do I get you to this
page as fast as possible?
这一点很重要。
And that's important.
但我也认为，特别是在现代单页应用程序的世界中，
But I also think that especially in the
world of modern single page applications,
我们需要考虑的好吧，你有申请，现在怎么办？
that we need to think about okay,
you have the application, now what?
对吧？
Right?
因此，我们还将讨论解析和JavaScript，以及
So we're also gonna talk about parsing and
JavaScript, and
编译性能，对吗？
compilation performance, right?
因为同样，特别是在单页面应用程序的情况下，
Because again, especially in
the case of a single page app,
我们将整个应用程序发送给您，您继续并编译它。
we are sending you this entire
application, you go ahead and compile it.
您继续解析整个源代码，并找出它的全部含义和
You go ahead and parse the entire source
code, and figure out what it all means and
然后构建应用程序。
then build the application.
如果我们发送的代码很难解析和编译。
If we send code that is very
hard to parse and compile.
我们写在一台3000美元的MacBook上。
We wrote it on a $3,000 MacBook.
这不是3000美元的MacBook，而是我的作品，
This is not a $3,000 MacBook,
but my work one,
我没有付钱，但我认为它很贵。
I didn't pay for it, but
I assume that it's expensive.
我们有这些昂贵的机器，拥有这些高性能的计算机。
We have these expensive machines that
have these high-powered computers.
但然后我们可以将其发送到移动设备，该设备的解析速度要慢得多
But we then can send it to a mobile device
that is a lot slower at parsing and
编译，对吧？
compiling, right?
但我们这边不能这么做。
But we can't do that on our side.
然后我们必须将其发送给用户，并希望他们也可以解析和
We have to then send it to the user and
hope that they can also parse and
快速编译。
compile it quickly.
因此，了解这些东西在引擎盖下是如何工作的，可以让我们进行某种程度的分析和
So learning how that stuff works under the
hood allows us to kind of one analyze and
做出一些决定，看看伤害在哪里，两个重构我们的代码
make some decisions and see where
the hurt is, and two refactor our code in
这样的方式使得解析器和编译器以及所有这些东西都变得更容易。
such a way that it is easier on the parser
and compiler and all those things.
最后，我们有渲染性能。
Finally, we have rendering performance.
所以我们把它放在页面上了。
So we have it on the page.
我们的JavaScript不仅仅是一个在他们的浏览器中运行的无JS程序，而是
Our JavaScript is not just simply a no JS
program that runs in their browser, but
它还操纵页面，显示用户界面。
also it is manipulating the page,
it's displaying a user interface.
对吧？我们的JavaScript不是生活在真空中，
Right?
Our JavaScript does not live in a vacuum,
而是必须处理dom和浏览器，
but instead has to deal with the dom and
the browser and
所有这些其他组件。
all of these other components.
所以弄清楚整个系统是如何工作的
So figuring out how that
entire system works and
如何确保我们不会碰到那里的大路障。
how to make sure we don't
hit large roadblocks there.
那么三种不同的表演，它们是否同样重要？
So three different kinds of performance,
are they equally as important?
我会争辩说是，但真正的答案是不，对吗？
I would argue yes, but
the real answer is no, right?
因为同样，应用程序需要做什么很重要，对吗？
Because again, it matters what your
application needs to do, right?
以及应用程序中的具体位置。
And where the pinpoints
in your application.
所以我们也会讲一点关于测量和
So we'll also talk a little
bit about measuring and
如何弄清楚这些事情。
how to figure those things out.
好的，非常酷。
All right, very cool.
所以我们将讨论一些需要考虑的数字。
So we're gonna talk a little bit about
some numbers to just think about.
我们今天不会对数字太着迷，因为我认为
We're not gonna obsessed to much about
numbers today, because I think it's
真的很难，好吧，每次互动都需要100毫秒。
really hard to, okay, every interaction
need to be 100 milliseconds.
你启动你的应用程序，然后你就有了两秒钟的互动。
You fire up your app and then you've
a got a two second interaction.
我放弃了，我要回家一天。
I give up, I'm going home for the day.
但心里有一些目标，我认为真的很有用。
But having some goals in mind is,
I think really useful.
所以Google有一个首字母缩写叫做RAIL。
So Google has this acronym called RAIL.
我猜他们可能还有其他人，比如骗子，或者其他类似的人，
I guess they could have had other ones
like liar, or anything along those lines,
但铁路是他们追求的目标。
but RAIL is the one they went for.
它基本上是一组考虑性能的基准，
And it's basically a set of benchmarks
to think about performance,
有效的目标。
effectively goals.
因此，Rails代表Response Animation Idle and Load。
So, RAIL stands for
Response Animation Idle and Load.
我们一会儿再看一遍。
And we'll look at those again in a second.
但这里又是回应部分。
But here's that response part again.
这就是人类感知相互作用的方式。
This is how humans perceive interactions.
我们以前见过。
We saw it before.
0到100毫秒，瞬时。
0 to 100 milliseconds, instantaneous.
十秒钟后，我要去别的地方，但是
After ten seconds,
I'm going somewhere else, but
即使在一秒钟之后，心理环境也会发生变化。
even after a second there's
a mental context switch.
这又是说也许我应该做些其他的事情。
Which again is that maybe I
should be doing something else.
所以我们要瞄准
So we wanna aim for
低于100毫秒。&gt；&gt；Steve Kinney：动画，
under 100 milliseconds.
&gt;&gt; Steve Kinney: Animations,
大多数屏幕，我认为新的iPad Pro有点不同，但是
most screens, I think the new iPad
Pro is a little bit different, but
我们的大多数屏幕以每秒60帧的速度刷新，
most of our screens refresh
at 60 frames a second,
在每一帧之间变成大约16毫秒。
which turns into about 16
milliseconds in between every frame.
这就是屏幕刷新的频率，所以你走得更快，
So that's how often the screen refreshes,
so you go any faster than that,
没关系，屏幕不会显示任何东西。
it doesn't matter,
the screen's not gonna show anything.
但你变得更慢，
But you get slower than that,
并且用户可以开始知道滚动变得有点不稳定。
and users can start to know that
the scrolling is getting a little janky.
或者拖拽和
Or the dragging and
掉下来，我工作的编辑变得有点怪异。
dropping, the editor that I worked
on is getting a little weird.
所以16毫秒真的很重要，
So it's like 16 milliseconds is really
kind of important to think about,
就是你想要一个新的画面出现在屏幕上，
is that you wanna get
a new frame to the screen,
如果你想让任何东西都有动画效果，让它看起来很好。
if you're trying to animate anything and
have it look good.
但那16毫秒都不是你的
But all those 16
milliseconds are not yours.
浏览器正在做其他事情，一些正在运行的Chrome扩展
The browser's doing other stuff,
some Chrome extensions that are running
正在做其他的事情，所以你必须分享这段时间。
are doing other stuff, so
you have to share that time.
IDLE是它的另一个部分，它基本上是任何不需要的东西
Idle is another part of it which is
basically anything that doesn't need to be
立即完成，尝试在用户什么都不做的时候做。
done immediately, try to do when
the user's not doing anything.
好的，现在他们正在阅读文章，现在去找任何令人毛骨悚然的跟踪软件
Okay, now they're reading the article, now
go get whatever creepy tracking software
你想放在那里弄清楚他们在做什么，对吗？
that you wanna put on there to figure
out what they are doing, right?
不要在初始页面加载时这样做，或者
Don't do that for the initial page load or
否则就没有什么可以追踪的了，因为他们已经走了。
else there is gonna be nothing
to track because they're gone.
如果你能在15毫秒内完成，很好，
And if you can get that done in
15 millisecond chunks, great,
因为如果他们做了什么，你就准备好了。
because then if they do do something,
you're ready to deal with that.
最后，加载。
Finally, Load.
如果我们能在一秒钟内看到整页那就太好了，
It would be great if we could get
the entire page under a second,
但除此之外，它是第一个有意义的油漆的理想选择。
but otherwise it's ideal for
first meaningful paint.
那么，第一幅有意义的画是什么呢？
So what is a first meaningful paint?
这真的取决于你的申请。
It really depends on your application.
如果你是推特，可能是中间时间线，或者提到或者其他什么，
If you are Twitter maybe it's that middle
timeline, or mentions or whatever first,
然后你可以得到小的侧边栏和搜索以及所有这些东西。
and then you can get the little sidebars
and the search and all of those things.
试图在不到一秒的时间内到达第一个非常重要的事情。
Trying to get to the first very
important thing in under a second.
这些都是需要考虑的重要问题。
Those are important to think about.
我们不会，就像我之前说的，
We're not going to, like I said before,
痴迷于他们，因为我可以告诉你，我拿了整个铁路模型。
obsess over them because I can tell
you I took the whole rail model.
我看着我工作的应用程序，几乎哭了，对吧？
I looked at the application I
worked on and almost cried, right?
因为这些都不是我喜欢的大型桌面应用的方式
Because like those were not anywhere near
the way that I like large desktop apps in
网络浏览器正常工作，对吧？
the web browser was working, right?
所以我会争辩说这是关于逐渐变好的，对吗？
So I would argue it's about progressively
getting a little better, right?
找出应用程序中受伤害的区域。
Figuring out where the areas of
hurt are in your application.
想办法，好吧，我知道这很慢。
Figuring out how to, okay,
I know this is slow.
这是第一步对吧？
That's step one, right?
第二步是弄清楚，好的，我知道如何在Chrome中读取性能时间表
Step two is figuring out, okay I know how
to read the performance timeline in Chrome
然后找出，想出一些假设来对它做些什么。
and figure out, come up with some
hypothesis of what to do about it.
然后第三步是对该做什么有一些想法，然后第四步是测量
And then step three is having some ideas
of what to do, and four is then measuring
看看它是变好了还是变坏了，以及沿着这些路线的东西。
to see if it got better or worse,
and stuff along those lines.
所以当我准备这个研讨会的时候，我写了这个简介
So when I was preparing this workshop,
I wrote this blurb of
原来是关于它的，并发送给我的一些同事。
originally what it was about and
sent it to some of my colleagues.
我的一位前同事，罗密卡，想出了另一个头衔
And one of my former co workers, Romeeka,
came up with an alternative title for
该研讨会名为“优化Web性能的策略当，
this workshop called, Strategies for
Optimizing Web Performance When,
老实说，你今天有5个会议
Honestly, You Have Like
5 Meetings Today and
必须选择正确的山丘来策略性地死亡。
Have to Choose the Correct Hills
upon Which to Strategically Die.
[笑]对吧？
[LAUGH] Right?
观看一些Google IO演示文稿是非常容易的，
It's very easy for, to watch some
Google IO presentation where it's like,
是的，我们将整个应用程序重写为一个进步的Web应用程序
yes we rewrote the entire application
as a progressive web app and
现在超快了
now it's super fast.
进步的网络应用程序实际上很酷，你完全应该在它们上看我的课程。
Progressive web apps are actually cool you
should totally watch my course on them.
但就好像这通常不是大改写不是的东西
But it's like that is usually not
something the big rewrite is not
你明天就能做的事，对吧？
something you're gonna be
able to do tomorrow right?
所以这里的目标是，考虑到当前的世界，考虑到当前的状态
So the goal here is, given the current
world, given the current state of
你正在做的事情，我们怎么让它更快？
the thing that you're working on,
how do we make it faster?
我们怎样才能让它变得更好？
How do we make it better?
我们怎样才能慢慢地重复这一点
And how do we repeat that until slowly but
我们肯定已经开始接近这些基准了吗？
surely we start approaching
those benchmarks?
所以重要的是要考虑什么对你来说是重要的。
So it's important to think
about what matters to you.
然后找出如何测量它，对吗？
And then figuring out how to measure it,
right?
所以我谈到，也许显示内容而不是泄漏内存，
So I talked about, maybe showing
content versus not leaking memory,
这很酷，但也很难作为一个已知的东西来表达，对吧？
that's cool, but it's also hard to
express as a known thing, right?
所以在你的应用程序中弄清楚什么是真正重要的事情，对吗？
So figure out in your application what
is actually the important thing, right?
因此，“纽约时报”可能会再一次关注第一个头条新闻的时间。
So again, New York Times might care
about the time to first headline.
Twitter可能会关心你写一条tweet需要多长时间。
Twitter might care about how long it
takes you to be able to write a tweet.
也许下次对我来说应该更长一些，对吧？
Maybe that should be longer for
me some other time, right?
也许我需要延迟一下，在我打字之前想一想我在推特上写的是什么
Maybe I need a delay to think about
what I'm tweeting before I type it
放进那个盒子里。
into that box.
但对于推特，他们可能想让我尽可能快地发推文。
But for Twitter they wanna probably
get me to tweet as fast as possible.
不管应用程序是什么，所以我在一个大的电子邮件编辑器上工作，对吗？
Whatever the application is, so
I work on a big email editor, right?
编辑器加载的时间，以便您可以开始拖动和
Time for the editor to load up so
you can start dragging and
加入你用来创建电子邮件的模块，对吗？
dropping in the modules that you
use to create the email, right?
这可能是我们最重要的部分，需要多长时间
That might be the important part for
us, how long does it take
在登录到您正在创建新的营销活动的点之间？
between log in to get to the point where
you're creating a new marketing campaign?
这将是一个重要的例子
That would be an example of something
that would be important for
我工作的应用程序。
the application that I work on.